Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Alisa Solomon and Nancy Ordover on American Eugenics; David Barsamian Interview with Edward Said (Partial Aircheck) [2003-022], 2003-08-17 (Box 17, Item 718_0627)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Nancy Ordover on American Eugenics [2003-050], 2003-08-17 (Box 23, Item 718_0979)
- Geoffrey Aronson on Israeli Occupation; Michael Karpman on Mass Budget Cuts to Social Services [2003-026], 2003-08-24 (Box 17, Item 718_0632)
- Re-airing Michael Zweig The Working Class Majority and Grace Paley Readings [2003-001], 2003-08-31 (Box 16, Item 718_0604)
- Michael Zweig on The Working Class Majority; Grace Paley Reads at Theater for the New City (TNC) Benefit [2003-078], 2003-08-31 (Box 34, Item 718_1004)
- Lorin Sklamberg on New Music Releases [2003-038], 2003-09-03 (Box 17, Item 718_0641)
- Amer Abdulhadi of Tariq Al Mahabbeh; Marge Piercy Reading "No One Came Home"; Julie Sandorf of Nextbook.org [2003-043], 2003-09-14 (Box 17, Item 718_0645)
- Edward Said NY Interview with David Barsamian, Part 1 [2003-070], 2003-09-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_4)
- Memories of Arthur Kinoy and Edward Said; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz with Abby Levine and Zaid Ali on Immigrant Rights Freedom Ride [2003-005], 2003-09-28 (Box 16, Item 718_0609)
- Lorin Sklamberg with Guest Sarah Aroeste; Sephardic Music [2003-021], 2003-10-05 (Box 17, Item 718_0626)
- Rabbi Amy Schwartzman on Jewish Meeting with Bush; Judith Sloan and Warren Lehrer on Crossing the BLVD; and Jennifer Bleyer and Matt Cowan on Heeb Magazine [2003-007], 2003-10-12 (Box 16, Item 718_0612)
- Marathon: Alisa Solomon with Tony Kushner on Wrestling with Zion; Readings by Grace Paley, Sarah Roy, Daniel Wolfe, and Naomi Klein, Part 1 [2003-006], 2003-10-19 (Box 16, Item 718_0610)
- Marathon: Alisa Solomon with Tony Kushner on Wrestling with Zion; Readings by Sarah Roy, Daniel Wolfe, Naomi Klein, Grace Paley, and Aurora Levins Morales, Part 2 [2003-039], 2003-10-19 (Box 16, Item 718_0611)
- Daniel Wolfe [2003-052], 2003-10-19 (Box 23, Item 718_0981)
- Non-Partisan Primary with Wayne Barrett and Debra Goldberg; Amram Mitzna on the Geneva Accord [2003-011], 2003-11-02 (Box 16, Item 718_0616)
- Edward Said, 40 Days After His Death (NYU Law School) [2003-064], 2003-11-03 (Box 18, Item 718_0687)
- Amram Mitzna [2003-068], 2003-11-03 (Box 18, Item 718_0692)
- Co-host Laura Schere on K-12 Education Changes; Michael Ratner on US Supreme Court Review of Guantanamo Cases [2003-003], 2003-11-16 (Box 16, Item 718_0608)
- Stephen Cohen on Mikhail Khodorkovsky's Arrest in Russia; Craig Smith on Istanbul Bombing; Ervand Abrahamian on Al-Qaeda [2003-019], 2003-11-23 (Box 17, Item 718_0623)
- Aharon Shabtai and Peter Cole; Nan Rubin Interviews Frederic Brenner [2003-036], 2003-11-30 (Box 17, Item 718_0639)
- Tim Judah on Last Jews of Baghdad [2003-076], 2003-11-30 (Box 23, Item 718_0987)
- Frieda Zames, Avi Lyon, and Jack Ryan on Disability Rights and Jewish Cemetery Strike, 2003-12-07 (Box 17, Item 718_0634)
- Holy Ground: Jewish Songs of Woody Guthrie with Lorin Sklamberg, Frank London, and Lisa Gutkin [2003-065], 2003-12-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0688)
- Myra Alperson on Food Markets for Holidays; Deidre Behar on Children's Books; Sandi DuBowski Interview [2003-066], 2003-12-21 (Box 18, Item 718_0690)
- Yaron Ezrahi on IDF Shootings of Anti-Wall Demonstrators, Sharon Corruption Scandal, and Policies/Future; Tamara Cohen on 30th Anniversary of the Jewish Catalogue [2003-065], 2003-12-28 (Box 18, Item 718_0689)
- Nan Rubin Interviews Daniel Levitas on The Terrorist Next Door; Alisa Solomon Interviews Amy and Elizabeth Ziff of BETTY Rules [2003-048], 2003-12-29 (Box 17, Item 718_0650)
- Janusz Makuch [2004-055] (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_5)
- Rabbi Arik Ascherman on Trial for Blocking a Bulldozer; Ghassan Hamdan of Palestine Medical Relief Committees in Nablus; Miriam of Jewish Women Watching [2004-041], 2004-01-04 (Box 18, Item 718_0731)
- Brother Joe Magallan on Guest Worker Initiative; Tribute to Enid Dame with Clare Kinberg and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz; Aviva Weintraub on the Jewish Film Festival [2004-049], 2004-01-11 (Box 18, Item 718_0739)
- Jeff Ruch on Religion in the Public Parks; Shana Liebman, Jonathan Ames, and Hal Sirowitz of the Heeb Jewish Storytelling Series [2004-003], 2004-01-18 (Box 17, Item 718_0654)
- Marathon: David Cole on Enemy Aliens; Cass Sunstein on Why Societies Need Dissent, Part 1 [2004-024], 2004-02-01 (Box 18, Item 718_0714)
- Marathon: David Cole on Enemy Aliens; Marcia Kuntz of Judicial Selection Project at the Alliance for Justice, Part 2 [2004-028], 2004-02-01 (Box 18, Item 718_0718)
- Alisa Solomon and Robert Kuttner Speak with Rabbi Paul Menitoff and Susan Calechman on America as a One-Party State and the Massachusetts Supreme Court Decision on Same-Sex Marriage [2004-023], 2004-02-08 (Box 18, Item 718_0713)
- Riv-Ellen Prell on Judith Steinberg Dean and the Media; Alicia Svigals, Susan Watts, and Pete Rushefsky on Upcoming Performances at Satalla [2004-022], 2004-02-15 (Box 18, Item 718_0712)
- Andre Schiffrin on French Legislation Prohibiting Religious Symbols in Public Schools; Rachel Leon on the Impact of Help America Vote Act on New York State and Voting Technology; Alisa Solomon Interviews Benjamin Hollander on Rituals of Truce and the Other Israeli [2004-050], 2004-02-22 (Box 18, Item 718_0740)
- Benjamin Hollander on Rituals of Truce and the Other Israeli [2004-050], 2004-02-22 (Box 18, Item 718_0741)
- Purim: Jenny Romaine and Martin Schwartz; Primary Election Roundup: Charles Lenchner, Ryan Karban, and Mark Green [2004-027], 2004-02-29 (Box 18, Item 718_0717)
- Lorin Sklamberg Music Show [2004-029], 2004-03-07 (Box 18, Item 718_0719)
- Phil Greene, Alana Newhouse, Chip Berlet on The Passion of the Christ and Left Behind; Ra'anan Alexandrowicz on James' Journey to Jerusalem [2004-026], 2004-03-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0716)
- Road to Peace [2004-011], 2004-03-15 (Box 18, Item 718_0701)
- Part 1: Road to Peace Conference, 15th Anniversary with Adnan Abdul Razek, Rabbi Roly Matalon, Donna Nevel, and Alisa Solomon; Pearl Gluck, Aaron Taub, and Basya Schechter on Divan [2004-004], 2004-03-21 (Box 18, Item 718_0694)
- Uri Avnery Interview (Partial); Road to Peace, Part 2: 15th Anniversary with Rabbi R. Matalon, Adnan Abdel-Razek, Donna Nevil, and Alisa Solomon; Sarah Yahm Interviews Esther Hugenholtz on European and American Jews and Israel [2004-025], 2004-03-28 (Box 18, Item 718_0715)
- Lorin Sklamberg - Pesach [2004-040], 2004-04-04 (Box 18, Item 718_0730)
- Parents' Circle: Bereaved Israeli and Palestinian Families with Robi Damelin; Yale Strom on Klezmer on Fish Street with Nan Rubin; Tribute to Richie Perez: Talk from Summer 1994 with Panama Alba [2004-042], 2004-04-11 (Box 18, Item 718_0732)
- Sidney Blumenthal on Condoleezza Rice and Bush Middle East Policy; Zachary Lockman on Legislative Threats to Middle East Centers; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interview with Loolwa Khazzoom and Ruth Knafo Setton on The Flying Camel [2004-043], 2004-04-18 (Box 18, Item 718_0733)
- Does a Jewish State Have a Future? Debating Israel in America: Tony Judt, Amos Elon, Alan Brinkley, and Raef Zreik [2004-021], 2004-04-20 (Box 18, Item 718_0711)
- Tami Gold and Doris Busch Boskey on Every Mother's Son and Police Brutality; Phyllis Bennis on Bush/Sharon Deal [2004-051], 2004-05-02 (Box 18, Item 718_0742)
- Phyllis Bennis on Israel/Palestine Repercussions in Region; Michael Lerner on Tikkun Lobby Day for Peace; Ujju Aggarwal and Delsa Rosso on Segregation in NYC Schools [2004-046], 2004-05-09 (Box 18, Item 718_0736)
- Tami Gold and Doris Busch Boskey on Every Mother's Son Documentary; Phyllis Bennis on Sharon/Bush Deal [2004-002], 2004-05-20 (Box 17, Item 718_0655)
- Ryan King on Life Sentences Report; Leslie Cagan on Protest Permit; Sarah Abrevaya Stein on Making Jews Modern [2004-039], 2004-05-30 (Box 18, Item 718_0729)
- Sherry Gorelick on Women in Black; Laura Whitehorn on David Gilbert's No Surrender and Political Prisoners; Ruth Messinger on Foundation and Government Grant Restrictions and on Darfur, Sudan; Vic Skulnik on Jewish Diaspora Film Festival [2004-016], 2004-06-06 (Box 18, Item 718_0706)
- Christine Marinoni of Alliance for Quality Education; Henry Foner on Death of Morris Schappes; Steve Schwerner on Michael Schwerner and Freedom Summer; Ben Addleman on Discordia at the Human Rights Watch Film Festival [2004-038], 2004-06-13 (Box 18, Item 718_0728)
- Nabila Espanioly [2004-020], 2004-06-15 (Box 18, Item 718_0710)
- Rabbi Marc Angel on the 350th Anniversary of Shearith Israel; RNC Activism Update with Miranda Nelson; Tony Judt "Does a Jewish State Have a Future?" Presentation at NYU [2004-044], 2004-07-04 (Box 18, Item 718_0734)
- Ruchama Marton and Michael Ratner on Use of Torture by US and Israel; Election Series: Taxation with Doug Henwood; RNC Activism Update with Miranda Nelson [2004-045], 2004-07-18 (Box 18, Item 718_0735)
- Judy Richardson on 1964 Democratic National Convention; Matt Borns on Boston Social Forum; Hannah Rosenthal and Kathy Goldman on Bush Poverty Policy; RNC Activism Update with Miranda Nelson (Partial) [2004-017], 2004-07-25 (Box 18, Item 718_0707)
- Deborah Meier on K-12 Education and "No Child Left Behind"; Kate Shaughnessy, Alma Flores, and Walnide Fabre on New American Freedom Summer; Rev. Victor Makari on Presbyterian Divestment from Israel [2004-032], 2004-08-08 (Box 18, Item 718_0722)
- Tribute to Yiddish Writers Killed by Stalin on 8/12/52; Natalia Indrimi and Francesco Spagnolo on The Other Modigliani Exhibition; Bush Report on Immigration with Aarti Sheham [2004-012], 2004-08-15 (Box 18, Item 718_0703)
- Naomi Klein on Economics of Iraq; Leslie Cagan on RNC Protests; Lynne Sharon Schwartz on New Short Story Collection [2004-006], 2004-08-22 (Box 18, Item 718_0696)
- Joe Goldman on Asociación Mutual Israelita Argentina (AMIA) Verdict; Ari Kagan on Assembly Primary Race in Brooklyn; Bush Report with Bill Henning on Labor Policy [2004-015], 2004-09-05 (Box 18, Item 718_0705)
- Joe Goldman on AMIA Bombing [2004-033], 2004-09-05 (Box 18, Item 718_0723)
- Bush Report: Barbara Bowen on Higher Education; Basya Schechter on Queen's Dominion [2004-014], 2004-09-12 (Box 18, Item 718_0704)
- Bush Report: Felon Disenfranchisement; Interviews with Former Felons by Sarah Yahm, Carol Powell, and Ryan King; Voting Rights with Elliot Mincberg; Update on Israel and Palestine with Adam Keller [2005-005], 2004-09-19 (Box 18, Item 718_0695)
- Bush's War on Women with Carla Goldstein; Naomi Klein and Avi Lewis on The Take [2004-031], 2004-09-26 (Box 18, Item 718_0721)
- Mik Moore and Operation Bubbe; Laura Rozen on American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) Investigation; Mark Hannay on Bush and Kerry Health Proposals (Partial) [2004-009], 2004-10-03 (Box 18, Item 718_0699)
- Alam PMRCC [2004-030], 2004-10-09 (Box 18, Item 718_0720)
- PHR UPMCC, Part 2 [2004-036], 2004-10-09 (Box 18, Item 718_0726)
- Bush Report: Rashid Khalidi and Josh Ruebner on Policy Toward Israel; Bedouins in Israel with Hannah Safran and Safa Abu-Rabia; Amit Gazi and Tali Zhak Interview on Neighbors by Israeli playwright, Hanoch Lev [2004-008], 2004-10-10 (Box 18, Item 718_0698)
- Jeremy Burton and E.J. Kessler on Jewish Voters in 2004; Bush Report: Environmental Policy with Hadar Susskind and Kurt Davies; David Van Taylor on With God on Their Side [2004-010], 2004-10-17 (Box 18, Item 718_0700)
- Marathon Show: Rob Boston, Aaron Lebowitz, Kirstin Moore, and Chloe Brier [2004-007], 2004-10-24 (Box 18, Item 718_0697)
- Esther Kaplan on God on Their Side; Rob Boston of Americans United for Separation of Church and State; Aaron Leibowitz of Darby, Montana, Kristin Moore of Reproductive Health Technology Project, and Rev. Chloe Breyer of Vote for Your Values [2004-037], 2004-10-24 (Box 18, Item 718_0727)
- Nan Rubin Interview with Aaron Lebowitz [2004-053], 2004-10-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_7)
- Spiegelman [2004-035], 2004-11-07 (Box 18, Item 718_0725)
- Jeremy Burton and E.J. Kessler on the Jewish Vote; Rashid Khalidi on Yasser Arafat's Death [2004-013], 2004-11-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0702)
- Columbia University Conference "Impasse? Alternative Voices in the Middle East": Jessica Benjamin Lila Abu-Lughod; Yossi Beilin, and Mahmood Mamdani, Tape 1 [2004-047], 2004-11-20 (Box 18, Item 718_0737)
- Columbia University Conference "Impasse? Alternative Voices in the Middle East": Yossi Beilin, Mahmood Mamdani, Tape 2 [2004-048], 2004-11-20 (Box 18, Item 718_0738)
- Remembering Seymour Melman with Murray Eden; Rabbi Michael Lerner on the Christian Right's Defense of Christmas; Max Blumenthal on Judith Reisman's Influence on Public Policy and the Right; Natalie Handel Poetry Reading at ABC No-Rio; 3 Cities Against the Wall [2004-034], 2004 November 24; 2004 December 26 (Box 18, Item 718_0724)
- Grace Paley Readings [2004-001], 2004-11-24 (Box 23, Item 718_0988)
- Grace Paley Benefit: 3 Cities Against the Wall (1) 3 Days and a Question (2) Afraid (3) Responsibility of the Poet [2004-052], 2004-11-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_8)
- Grace Paley Benefit: 3 Cities Against the Wall (1) 3 Days and a Question (2) Afraid (3) Responsibility of the Poet [2004-052], 2004-11-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_67)
- Nan Rubin Interviews Art Spiegelman on In the Shadow of No Towers; Gerard Jones on Men of Tomorrow; Esther Kaplan Interviews Roya Hakakian [2004-018], 2004-11-28 (Box 18, Item 718_0708)
- Roya Hakakian on Journey from the Land of No; Nan Rubin Interviews Art Spiegelman on In The Shadow of No Tower, 2004-11-28 (Box 34, Item 718_1005)
- Nan Rubin Interviews Art Spiegelman on In The Shadow of No Tower [2004-054], 2004-11-28 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_6)
- Sarah Yahm Interviews Sarah Henry, Bernie and Honey Kassoy, and Bea Simpsons on Radicals in the Bronx Exhibition; Roya Hakakian and Ervand Abrahamian on Iraq; Larry Miller on Israel Divestment Vote in Somerville, MA [2004-019], 2004-12-12 (Box 18, Item 718_0709)
- Dahlia Sachs, Disc 1 [2015-015], circa 2005-2013 (Box 20, Item 718_1011)
- Eileen Clancy Eye Witness Video on NYPD Surveillance; Nan Rubin Interviews Israeli Broadcaster Haim Yavin, 2005-01-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_49)
- Ruth Messinger on Tsunami Disaster; the U.S. as a Christian Nation with Mark Crispin Miller and Chip Berlet; Michael Bronski on the Death of Susan Sontag [2005-022], 2005-01-02 (Box 19, Item 718_0763)
- Campaign for Fiscal Equity (CFE) Lawsuit Update with Noreen Connell and Christine Marinoni; Michael Ratner on Gonzales Nomination for Attorney General; Dara Silverman on Upcoming Issues [2005-015], 2005-01-09 (Box 18, Item 718_0762)
- Omar Barghouti and Yifat Susskind on the Palestinian Elections; Daniel Lazare on American Democracy; Naomi Braine on Counter-Inaugural Actions [2005-021], 2005-01-16 (Box 18, Item 718_0761)
- Phyllis Bennis on Bush's 2nd Term Foreign Policy Plans; David Kertzer on Catholic Churches and Jewish Children (Partial) [2005-023], 2005-01-23 (Box 19, Item 718_0764)
- Yaron Zilberman on Watermarks; Barak Goodman on The Fight; Thomas Weber on the Lodz Ghetto Album; David Kertzer on Catholic Church and Sheltered Jews During WWII, Part 1 [2005-020], 2005-01-30 (Box 18, Item 718_0759)
- Marathon Show: Barak Goodman on The Fight; Yaron Zilberman on Watermarks; David Kertzer on Catholic Church and Jewish Children Protected During WWII; Thomas Weber on The Lodz Ghetto Album, Part 2 [2005-024], 2005-01-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0765)
- Anatol Lieven on America Right or Wrong, 2005-02-11 (Box 19, Item 718_0770)
- Remembering Ossie Davis; Neve Gordon on Sharon-Abbas Negotiations and Recent Palestine-Israel Events; Nathaniel Popper on Former USSR Jewish Immigration to Germany and Changed Policy; Jenny Romaine on Jewish Performance Tradition [2005-016], 2005-02-20 (Box 18, Item 718_0760)
- Marcia Falk, translator of "Spectacular Difference" poems by Zelda; Rabbi Brian Walt on Anti-Torture Campaign; Henry Foner with Carol Smith on The Struggle for Free Speech at CCNY, 1931-42 Exhibition at CUNY Graduate Center [2005-036], 2005-02-27 (Box 19, Item 718_0777)
- CUNY Graduate Center: Ammiel Alcalay, Doug Ashford, and Steve Kurtz [2005-034], 2005-03-04 (Box 19, Item 718_0775)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interview with Josef Grodzinsky on In the Shadow of the Holocaust [2005-014], 2005-03-05 (Box 18, Item 718_0755)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Ruth Linn on Escaping Auschwitz [2005-031], 2005-03-05 (Box 19, Item 718_0772)
- Moacyr Scliar (Partial); Alix Ryabov of Iraqi Veterans Against the War; Henry Foner with David Margolick on Forthcoming Book on the Joe Louis vs. Max Schmeling Fights [2005-002], 2005-03-06 (Box 18, Item 718_0743)
- Moacyr Scliar with Alisa Solomon [2005-005], 2005-03-09 (Box 18, Item 718_0746)
- Leslie Kielson on Anti-War Movement; Steve Kurtz Speaking at CUNY Graduate Center; Moacyr Scliar with Alisa Solomon on The Centaur in the Garden [2005-019], 2005-03-13 (Box 18, Item 718_0758)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Moacyr Scliar on The Centaur in the Garden [2005-057], 2005-03-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_43)
- Kurtz [2005-056], 2005-03-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_44)
- Phyllis Bennis on Lebanon, Syria, and Iran; Stephen F. Cohen on Democratization and Anti-Semitism in Russia [2005-007], 2005-03-20 (Box 18, Item 718_0748)
- Eugene Marlow on Making the Music Our Own with Alicia Svigals, Aaron Alexander, and Alan Watsky [2005-011], 2005-03-27 (Box 18, Item 718_0752)
- Erline Brown and Sarah Strand on Domestic Worker Bill; Mike Moore on Health Care Security Act; Rose Schneiderman on JTS Action; Rabbi Tamara Cohen on Women in Judaism Report [2005-013], 2005-04-03 (Box 18, Item 718_0754)
- Gaza Students Hekmat K. Bessiso and Adil El-Ghoul [2005-028], 2005-04-06 (Box 19, Item 718_0769)
- Jacqueline Rose on The Question of Zion [2005-032], 2005-04-07 (Box 19, Item 718_0773)
- Michael Massing and Mark Weisbrot on Paul Wolfowitz Being Named to World Bank; Rashid Khalidi and Ammiel Alcalay on Mideast Studies Attack at Columbia University and Campaign Against Academic Freedom [2005-009], 2005-04-10 (Box 18, Item 718_0750)
- Michel Warschawski of Alternative Information Center in Jerusalem and author of On the Border [2005-006], 2005-04-17 (Box 18, Item 718_0747)
- Hekmat K. Bessiso and Adil El-Ghoul on Conditions in Gaza; Grace Paley Reading at ABC No-Rio Benefit [2005-008], 2005-04-24 (Box 18, Item 718_0749)
- Gaza with Hekmat K. Bessiso and Adil El-Ghoul [2005-050], 2005-04-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_35)
- Tony Kushner on Arthur Miller; Deborah Lipstadt on History on Trial; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Yosef Grodzinsky on In the Shadow of the Holocaust and Zionists in WWII Displaced Persons Camps [2005-030], 2005-05-01 (Box 19, Item 718_0771)
- Yosef Grodzinsky Interview on Book In the Shadow of the Holocaust [2005-053], 2005-05-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_33)
- Marc Perelman and Co-host Aniruddha Das on Israel/China Arms Deal; Jack Jacobs, Larry Bush, and Barney Zumoff on Jewish Currents and Workmen's Circle Merger (Partial) [2005-004], 2005-05-08 (Box 18, Item 718_0745)
- Marathon: Anatol Lieven on America Right or Wrong; Jacqueline Rose on The Question of Zion [2005-027], 2005-05-15 (Box 19, Item 718_0768)
- Anatol Lieven on America Right or Wrong; Jacqueline Rose on The Question of Zion [2005-078], 2005-05-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_46)
- Victor Navasky and E.L. Doctorow at CUNY Graduate Center [2005-037], 2005-05-25 (Box 19, Item 718_0778)
- Tony Klug on UK Academic Boycott of Israeli Universities; David Dorfman and Frank London on Older Testaments at Joyce Theater; Helen Schaub on Special Touch Organizing Campaign; Mary Beth Maxwell of American Rights at Work [2005-010], 2005-05-29 (Box 18, Item 718_0751)
- British Academic Boycott of Israeli Scholar, Tony Klug; David Dorfman and Frank London on Older Testaments at Joyce Theater; Helen Schaub on Special Touch Organizing Campaign; Mary Beth Maxwell of American Rights at Work [2005-038], 2005-05-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_9)
- Peter Kwong on Expatriates in China and Death of Israel Epstein; Ami Eden on FBI Investigation of American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) and AIPAC Conference; Steven Weiss on Conflict between Orthodox and Other Jews in Lawrence, Long Island School Board Elections [2005-033], 2005-06-05 (Box 19, Item 718_0774)
- Peter Hart on Bush Administration Efforts to Limit Dissenting Views on Public Broadcasting and Their Middle East Coverage; Udi Ofer on Patriot Act; Bruni Burris and Cynthia Madansky on Human Rights Watch Film Festival [2005-018], 2005-06-12 (Box 18, Item 718_0757)
- Peter Hart on CPB/NPR/PBS Middle East Coverage; Udi Ofer on Efforts to Extend Sunset Provisions and Expand Patriot Act; Bruni Burris and Cynthia Madansky on Still Life and Human Rights Watch Film Festival [2005-034], 2005-06-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_10)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interview with Ilan Stavans; Sephardic Literature Anthology [2005-003], 2005-06-29 (Box 18, Item 718_0744)
- Ruth Messinger on Central America Free Trade Agreement (CAFTA); Mike Weinstein and Jeremy Leaming on Religious Discrimination at Air Force Academy; Josh Norek and Abraham Velez of Hip Hop Hoodios [2005-017], 2005-07-03 (Box 18, Item 718_0756)
- Ruth Messinger on CAFTA; Air Force Academy Religious Discrimination with Mike Weinstein and Jeremy Leaming; Hip Hop Hoodios with Josh Norek and Abe Velez [2005-041], 2005-07-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_11)
- Amira Hass at Barnard; Victor Navasky and E.L. Doctorow in Conversation at CUNY Grad Center; Open Phones [2005-040], 2005-07-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_12)
- Amira Hass Talk at Barnard; Victor Navasky in Dialogue with E.L. Doctorow at CUNY Grad Center [2005-079], 2005-07-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_48)
- Phyllis Snyder on John Roberts Nomination to the Supreme Court; Karen Armstrong "Fundamentalism: The Fear and the Rage" Presentation at CUNY Graduate Center [2005-025], 2005-07-31 (Box 19, Item 718_0766)
- Phyllis Snyder on John Roberts Nomination to US Supreme Court; Karen Armstrong "Fundamentalism: The Fear and the Rage" Presentation [2005-061], 2005-07-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_14)
- Tribute to Frieda Zames; Chip Berlet on Millennialist and Apocalyptic Influences on Dominionism; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Ilan Stavans on The Schocken Book of Modern Sephardic Literature [2005-062], 2005-08-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_14)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Ilan Stavans on Schocken Book of Modern Sephardic Literature [2005-077], 2005-08-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_45)
- Dara Silverman on Racial Profiling; Gila Svirsky on International Women in Black Conference in Jerusalem; Carol Delton on Bar/Bat Mitzvah for Children with Disabilities [2005-026], 2005-08-14 (Box 19, Item 718_0767)
- Dara Silverman on Racial Profiling on NYC Subways; Gila Svirsky on International Women in Black Conference; Carol Delton on Bar/Bat Mitzvah for Children with Disabilities [2005-064], 2005-08-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_16)
- Jessica Montell on Gaza Withdrawal; Larry Cohler-Esses on AIPAC Indictments; Sarah Henry on Tolerance and Identity: Jews in Early NY at Museum of the City of New York [2005-063], 2005-08-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_15)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz with Lynne Sharon Schwartz on The Writing on the Wall [2005-074], 2005-08-22 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_38)